And let's talk about brokerage reports.
Vamakshi has joined us with the complete
update. Vamakshi, good morning. Tell us.
We will start with Bajaj Finance. A
report is coming from UBS
and it is highlighting that the overall
competitive intensity in the space is
increasing in consumer loans. This is under
appreciated and in fact the valuations are
already not factoring in the
quality of their customer base. This is also
picking up and especially the
company will have to focus on cross selling if
they have to post incremental growth.
Largely keeping all these factors in mind,
UBS has
increased bajajelectricals.com to ₹10 per
share. Apart from this, ICICI
Lobar will be the next stock on our radar.
Morgan Stanley says that the
company has reported weaker profits than expected
because the company has booked lower capital gains. The
management has maintained the guidance of the
combined ratio of 102 to 25. The management has
said that early
Signs of increased competitive intensity appear to be
materializing.
Healthy business growth
is also expected in the motor segment. Overall,
Morgan Standley has maintained its overweight rating on II Lombard in 25. Due to this, Morgan Standley has
maintained its overweight rating on II Lombard.
LTTS will be the next stock on our radar.
Morgan Standley says that the
company has reported weaker numbers than expected,
but management commentary, especially on demand,
appears to be quite positive. The deal pipeline
is strong, and recent deal wins are also positive
factors. Overall,
they say that considering the stock's
outperformance, material
acceleration growth may be visible.
If this is absent in 25, the stock
may underperform. Overall, Morgan Standley has an underweight rating on LTTS.
Finally, we will focus on the cement sector.
Morgan Standley says that India's
cement industry is in a multi-year demand
cycle. Capacity addition is quite strong,
but utilization levels may also remain high.
Overall, they say that UltraTech is  Dalam
Bharat Grasim A has an overweight rating,
although they have upgraded their rating on Amruja Cement and ACC.
Therefore, we are also keeping an eye on the cement sector.
Okay, so these are some brokerage reports
where the focus will be. Thank you Vamakshi
for giving this complete update. Now, let us quickly present
some trading ideas to you.
When we spoke to Devang in the morning,
he
advised to go bullish on Petronet LNG and ITC. And it is
interesting. Today, many
experts are looking bullish on ITC. The first
call we are getting from Rail Gear Broking
is ITC. Here they are
looking at a target of 488. Place a stop loss
of 464 and there is a sell advice in UPL. The
target is 552. The stop loss will be 570.
Kotak Securities has advised to go bullish on GSPL
and
you can buy here for a target of 575. The stop loss will be
434. The second call is to go bullish on GAIL at
173.  For the target of ₹
5997, place a stop loss of ₹ 5847. JM Finance has
advised to go bullish on Apollo Hospitals and
here they are looking at targets of ₹ 5997.
Place a stop loss of ₹ 5847. Finance
also advises to buy in ITC.
For the target of ₹ 492, the stop loss
is ₹ 467. Finally,
Investmart for Health is also here. They have
advised to go bullish on MOIL.
For the target of ₹ 360, the stop loss is ₹ 330. And
ITC is also on their radar. The target will be ₹ 488.
Place a stop loss of ₹ 467. So today we are
seeing that definitely keep an eye on ITC.
Many experts are advising to buy here
because yesterday in the last few
hours, a great rally was also seen here,
so go ahead with the rally.
Do keep an eye on ITC today from the trading point of view.